I got in super travel when was this four
days ago oh I was I was in a third-world
country doing stand-up was it called
Little Rock Arkansas and nobody's from
Arkansas are they hey I forgot to ask
nobody okay are you okay I'm so Hardy I
never wanted to offend anybody I really
am sorry if you really are I will speak
slower
if you're if you're really I don't know
if you're from Little Rock but if you
are backing me up like after the show
tell because I was just flying out the
Little Rock Arkansas Airport which I
didn't realize they just changed the
name to the Bill and Hillary Clinton
International Airport well you guys are
getting icy on me really quick everybody
calm down I am NOT going to make fun of
the Clintons okay this is not about them
at all
okay I don't know if that no I will
never make fun of the Clint I am the
last person that wants to wake up with a
mysterious self-inflicted gunshot wound
[Applause]
this is a story about the airport I
didn't even know they changed the name
evidently it like took forever because
they had a big voting process and the
Russians got involved and but it's a
great airport it really is it's
professionally Ron it's all paid staff
there are no interns and
this is what got me true this is a true
story I showed up at that morning and I
didn't know they change and they were
like welcome to the Bill and Hillary
Clinton International Airport may I see
your boarding pass and I couldn't help
it I was like aw man they emailed it to
me but it got deleted
I'm glad you guys are laughing cuz all I
remember after that moment was his hands
are cold
but I do I love doing this so I thank
you guys I'll be over there if you guys
want to hang out afterwards I really
love that you guys support Drybar comedy
because it's so important to do clean
comedy not be doing this for a while I'm
gonna close my last favorite traveling
story I was in Phoenix doing what you
normally do sweating yeah I'm sorry I
love people from Phoenix but they're all
I good to draw heat and I'm like yeah so
is a welding torch I don't want that
[Music]
but this was years ago is right when the
iPhone first came out remember when the
iPhone came out and it just changed
everybody's lives but it does it does
everything like you know even before
they introduced me I knew we were taping
so I was nervous so I was back there
using the deodorant app and I know
that's a cheesy joke but I like to tell
it because some people laugh but there's
always a few of you that's like does it
do that and if you're from Arkansas
you're like what's the odorant but when
the iPhone first came out when it first
came out I didn't know how to I didn't
know what to do with it
I didn't know anything about it but
thankfully my oldest was 7 so he did and
that's not a joke he made a ringtone for
me I didn't even know you I didn't even
know about ringtones he made a ringtone
I loved being a dad and he was like the
ringtone was hello dad pick up your
phone and so I was like listening to it
I was getting ready to fly back and I
was listening to it and I was about to
go through the little metal detectors
and so his Tom so I put my phone in the
bag and I guess the TSA guy saw me mess
with my bag so he opens it up he didn't
even see the phone I have some other
stuff in there he opened it up and he
got lays eyes big and I said well what
do I have in my bag and he pulled out a
tube of toothpaste and he's like
Buddha's douche it was like a that's
toothpaste what are you from West
Virginia and
he got really mad because he was and he
yelled at me he goes you can't fly with
toothpaste and I was like dude okay
Colin I've never been yelled at by TSA I
was like calm down I didn't think it
through but I totally agree take it
bleed me I don't want anybody jumping up
in the middle of the flight and brushing
everybody's teeth is that really a
threat or their tartar terrorists out
there right yeah why would they turn now
gargle go all up
it wasn't even terrorists like
toothpaste I don't understand if it was
like a more scope but but I'll close
with this is my favorite traveling story
he took the toothpaste and he's just
staring at me and he takes my bag and he
sets it on the conveyer belt and it
starts going in the x-ray machine he's
just staring at me and as soon as the
bag goes in the x-ray machine someone
called me and all of a sudden you hear
coming out of the bag hello dad he was
like a Sarah kid I was like calm down
he doesn't have toothpaste hey did you
know that Drybar comedy has their own
app download it right now to watch save
and share clips and watch my whole
special I hope you enjoy it